

DIGITAL MARKETING SPECIALIST



CONTACT

- +966-595-632-609
- 🗹 alamgir.inu96@gmail.com
- Saudi Arabia Riyadh
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/alam gir-khan-91933633b

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Javascript
- Modern Javascript (ES6+)
- Shopify
- React
- React Native
- Redux
- Git & github
- Object-Oriented Programming
- Social media advertising
- E-Commerse
- Digital Marketing
- Online ads Strategy
- Meta Business Suite
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Wordpress

PROFILE

Talented, task-driven professional with 4+ years of experience in web design and digital marketing. across different industries. Provided with a record of success in constantly identifying and providing the technological needs of companies through ingenious innovation. Proficient in WordPress, Shopify, designing and running ads, creating the user interface, solving simple and complex issues, and implementing new features based on user feedback, and I am specialized in digital marketing

WORK EXPERIENCE

Smartrankr.com
Web developer & Digital marketer

2023 - Present

- Buy a PHP script from CodeCanyon, buy a domain name (smartrankr.com), and then host on Hostinger.
- Search Engine Optimization for smartrankr.com to optimize website for search engines to improve visibility.
- Write SEO-optimized content for smartrankr.com
- Manage paid ad campaigns, run paid ads for SmartRankr, and create social media pages.

IDM Pakistan Web developer & Digital marketer 2022 - 2023

- (SEO) Search Engine Optimization: optimize website for search engines to improve visibility.
- Social Media Marketing: Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn, Twitter, and TikTok.
- PPC (Pay-Per-Click): Manage paid ad campaigns and run paid ads.
- Understand the meta-business suit and also work on audience targeting and bid strategies.
- Creating and Managing E-commerce store (Shopify)
- Brand Awarnes and creating content calender.

aitechfriend.com Manage & Own this website

2021- 2022

- This website for to help entrepreneurs and online startups. I created this website by myself to grow their brand or client brand easy for marketers
- Manage social media (Facebook, Instagram, TikTok) and maintain social consistency

EXPERTIES

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React.js
- · Object-oriented Programming
- Facebook ads
- Wordpress
- Shopify

HOBBIES

- · Books Reading
- Playing Cricket
- Cooking

LANGUAGES

- English (Conversational)
- Urdu (Fluent)
- Poshto (Fluent)

- Create and manage the marketing budget, ensuring efficient allocation of resources and optimizing ROI.
- Oversee market research to identify emerging trends, customer needs, and competitor strategies.
- Develop and maintain strong relationships with partners, agencies, and vendors to support marketing initiatives.
- Working on Excel and different tools to manage data

Impact software solution Web developer & social media manager

2020 - 2021

2013 - 2015

- Develop and create react and react native projects, design and establish the user-friendly website
- Establish an interactive and dynamic website. Eye-catching and maximum user experience
- Learn Functional Programming, Object oriented Programming, react, redux and modern JavaScript (ES6+) and working on different projects.
- I also created a professional website in WordPress with Elementor page builder
- Created Professional E-commerce stores on Shopify with research and finding winning products
- Develop comprehensive marketing strategies and campaigns that align with the company's goals and objectives.
- Monitor brand consistency across marketing channels and materials.



EDUCATION

Bachelor in software enginering	2016 - 2020
SIqra National University Peshawer	
GPA: 2.7 / 4.0	

Tipu Model School and college | Swat Pakistan

Percentage: 72% / 100%

Secondary certifictation

School certification 2011 - 2013

Criscent Public School | Karachi Pakistan

Percentage: 80% / 100%